[
    {
        "id": 0,
        "question": "For every person in this room, there is at least one characteristic that they have",
        "answerIndex": 0,
        "wrongAnswers": [
            "There is a person in this room that has not one characteristic",
            " For all the people in this room, each one of them has at least one characteristic",
            "There is not a person in this room that has not one characteristic",
            "There is a person in this room that has one characteristic"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "There exist a triangle, such that the sides are even",
        "answerIndex": 2,
        "wrongAnswers": [
            "there exists a triangle, so that one of the sides is even",
            "for all triangles, at least one of the sides is odd",
            "for all triangles, none of the sides are even",
            "for all triangles, at least one of the sides is even"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "There is a country in Asia",
        "answerIndex": 3,
        "wrongAnswers": [
            "for all countries in Asia, it is none in Asia",
            "for all countries in Asia, there is one in Asia",
            "for all countries in Africa, there is none in Africa",
            "for all countries in Asia, there is none in Asia"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "If I don't use a comma after the initial clause, then I should use commas to separate the two clauses",
        "answerIndex":2,
        "wrongAnswers": [
            "I used a comma after the initial clause and I should not have used a comma to separate the two clauses",
            "I should have used a comma after the initial clause and I should not have used a comma to separate the two clauses",
            "There is a comma after the initial clause, and I should have used a comma to separate the two clauses",
            " I used a comma after the initial clause or I should not have used a comma to separate the two clauses"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "There exists an integer n for which n is prime",
        "answerIndex": 0,
        "wrongAnswers": [
            " For all integers n, none is prime",
            "There is an integer n, so that it is prime",
            "For all integers n, one is prime",
            " For all integers n, there exist an integer p that is not prime"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Jenny is shorter than me or the sky is not blue",
        "answerIndex": 2,
        "wrongAnswers": [
            " for all people, the sky is not blue and Jenny is taller than that person",
            "Jenny is not taller than me and the sky is not blue",
            "Jenny is taller than me and the sky is blue",
            "Jenny is taller than me or the sky is blue"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "There are some students who are working class that have lower rates of recognizing words in print",
        "answerIndex": 0,
        "wrongAnswers": [
            "For all students, some of the students are working class and have lower rates of recognizing words in print",
            " For all students, some of the students are not working class and have higher rates of recognizing words in print",
            "For some students, none of the students are working class and they have higher rates of recognizing words in print",
            " For all students, some of the students are working class or have lower rates of recognizing words in print"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Kristyn is a female and blue jays are canada's national bird",
        "answerIndex": 3,
        "wrongAnswers": [
            "Kristyn is a female and robins are Canada's national bird",
            " For all females, Kristyn is not a female and for all birds, robins are not Canada's national bird",
            "Kristyn is not a female and robins are not canada's national bird",
            "Kristyn is not a female or robins are not canada's national bird"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "For every natural number, there exists a finite number that is greater than it",
        "answerIndex": 0,
        "wrongAnswers": [
            "There exists a natural number, so that there is no finite number that is greater than it",
            "There does not exist a finite number that's greater than this",
            " for all natural numbers, there is at least one other number that is greater",
            "There doesn't exist a natural number, so that there is a finite number that is greater than it"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "For every natural number, there is an integer that can be multiplied to it with no remainder",
        "answerIndex": 1,
        "wrongAnswers": [
            "There is an integer that can be multiplied to a natural number with no remainder",
            "There is a natural number, so that there is no integer that can be multiplied to it with no remainder",
            " There exist an infinite number of natural numbers, and for all numbers in this infinite set, there are integers that can be multiplied to it with no remainder",
            "is a natural number, so that there is no tetrahedron that can be inscribed in a cube with no remainder"
        ]
    }
]